Thank you so much for enrolling in my course I am honored.
Now if you have any questions along the way while you are taking my training please do not hesitate
to send me a text message or email me or whichever way that you for to contact me.
Another thing I do want to ask you is that nowadays you to me ask you for a course rating or review
very early probably you would watch my videos for 15 or 20 minutes and you will get a pop up window
to rate my course.
If you think that my course does not want Five-Star yet then please click on Skip and have it remind
you to the end of this course.
Then you should decide whether my course what Five-Star or not.
So let's get started.